JADEN KING-DOYLES

JUNIOR FULL-STACK DEVELOPER

iadenbusiness@hotmail.com

jubzcodes.github.io/portfolio/

905-442-5148

Oshawa, ON

SKILLS

PROGRAMMING LANGUAGES: Javacript, JSX, Ruby, SQL FUNDAMENTAL TECH SKILLS: HTML, CSS, SCSS LIBRARIES: React.JS, iQuery, AJAX, Axios FRAMEWORKS: Express, Github, Repl.it DATABASES: PostgreSQL

EDUCATION

Lighthouse Labs Diploma Full-Stack Web Development 2022

Real Estate and Mortgage Institute of Canada

Certification Mortgage Agent 2022

Durham College Diploma Pre-Health Sciences Pathway 2020

Aug. 2021 to Current

Aug. 2019 to May 2020

Dec. 2021 to Dec. 2021

Oshawa. ON Oct. 2020 to Nov. 2021

Aurora, ON

Oshawa. ON Oct. 2018 to Mar. 2020

Whitby, ON Apr. 2018 to Oct. 2018

Mar. 2020 to Sept. 2020

SUMMARY

I was working various jobs in different industries for 4+ years and decided to make a change. I have now turned full-stack developer in hopes of creating and building new products for the forever growing tech industry. Partnering with colleagues during my time as a developer, my mentor-ship, collaboration and resilience was a critical factor in the efficiency of the group. As I would help fellow classmates understand difficult material, direct projects by overseeing which group members would execute certain features. Along with finding libraries and methods to improve functionality of the projects.

PROJECTS

INTERVIEWER SCHEDULER Jan. 2022 to Jan. 2022

React application that allows users to book and cancel interviews using an API with a Websocket server for real time experience.

Stack: React, Javascript, PostgreSQL, Axios, SCSS, Storybook, Jest

Stack: Express, Javascript, SCSS, PostgreSQL, jQuery

Web application that allows registered users to turn any Url into a short Url. Logged in users were able create, edit and delete their own Urls

Web application that allows user to tweet messages to the dashboard

Stack: Javascript, jQuery, AJAX, HTML, CSS

EMPLOYMENT

RIIPEN Mar. 2022 to Apr. 2022. Mar. 2022 to Apr. 2022 Web Developer

My developer team and i coordinated with two employers to create three projects.

- Marketing digital solutions website using React and JavaScript.
- Buy and sell advertising website using React and JavaScript.
- · Several landing pages for https://indigrowthhealth.com using Wordpress

GIANT TIGER

TACO BELL

SHOELESS JOES

This role taught me to be self-efficient and work on my own accord with lack of supervision.

· Checked and sign off on deliveries that were sent to the store, then processed the items for distribution on the sales floor.

- Conducted quality checks for all the items in the produce department while assisting customers to keep the sales floor in order.
- Aided the cashiers in checking out customers when line-ups were long.

Landscaping taught me the discipline of sleeping and eating sufficiently in order to be prepared for the workday ahead.

· Combined strengths with colleagues to renovate condos and suburban homes.

· Operated the excavator.

FAIHST. WERNER E LIMITED

- Replaced soil and tarmac with new soil or gravel before we interlocked or sodded lawns, backyards or driveways.
- Use multiple machines to build stone walls for condos and factories.

Store associate Working at Taco Bell showed me how to deescalate toxic work environments and hostile situations.

• During rush hours i made the food to serve to customers and monitored our inventory of food prepared for serving and instructed colleagues to restock when supplies were low.

- When staff was short i would occupy the roles of drive-thru and front cash.

· Compromise with upset customers to resolve complaints.

This was my first job where I learned teamwork and how to adjust to a work environment.

- Prepped serving sizes for the lunch and dinner rush.
- Switched between roles of line cook and dishwasher depending the quantity of customers.
- Was given the role of making a variety desserts whenever i was on shift.

Awarded to students who completed the course with a 3.6 - 4.0 average

AWARDS

Durham College HONOUR ROLL May 2020

Nov. 2021 to Feb. 2022

in /jaden-king-doyles

O JubzCodes

Jan. 2022 to Jan. 2022

Web application that allows users to create, attempt and share a guizzes with other users

Stack: Express, Javascript, Node.JS, Bootstrap, CSS

Feb. 2021 to Feb. 2021 **TWFFTFR**